The pipe name could not be found. You may encounter this error when you reference a pipe
The pipe name could not be found. 你可能在範本中參考某個管道時遇到此錯誤
and a template that has either not been imported, or not been named properly. Just like components
它可能沒有匯入或正確命名
and directives, pipes must be declared or imported in an ngModule. In addition, when referenced in a
就像元件和指令一樣，管道也必須在 ngModule 中宣告或匯入
template, the name must match the name specified in the pipe decorator. Angular uses the name in
另外，當在範本中參考時，此名字必須與管道裝飾器中指定的名字相同
a template to determine which pipe to execute. That means every pipe must have a name and the
這意味著每個管道都必須有一個名字，而且
name must be unique to that ngModule. Let's start by taking a look at a simple reproduction and
該名字在所屬的 ngModule 中必須是唯一的 讓我們看一個簡單的錯誤重現及其解決方案
solution, then we'll review pipes in greater detail to understand why this error occurs
然後，我們會更詳細的研究管道，以便理解為何會發生本錯誤
in our code base. You'll notice we're referencing a pipe with the name of truncate, however the red
你可能注意到我們在使用 truncate 這個名字來參考此管道
underline in VSCode is telling us that Angular cannot find a pipe with that name. If you don't
不過 VSCode 中的紅色下劃線告訴我們：Angular 無法找到具有這個名字的管道
see the error in VSCode, you might also find it in the terminal or in the browser console. In either
如果你沒有在 VSCode 中看到本錯誤，也會在終端視窗或瀏覽器控制檯中看到
case, the stack trace will direct you to the template file that is causing the issue. In order
無論哪種情況，堆疊追蹤都會為你指出發生此問題的範本
to fix the issue, we'll first want to verify that the pipe is available in the appropriate ngModule.
要想修復本錯誤，我們先要驗證此管道在 ngModule 中是可用的
In this case we're attempting to use the pipe in the AppModule. Because it's a custom pipe
這個例子中，我們試圖在 AppModule 中使用此管道
that we're developing in this project, it needs to be in the declarations for this Module just like
因為它是我們正在開發的專案中的自訂管道，所以它需要 像元件或指令一樣，宣告在此模組中
a component or directive. Now in other cases, the pipe may be exported by a different Module
另一些例子中，管道可能是由其它模組或第三方包匯出的
or exported from a third party package, in which case you may need to import that Module
那種情況下，你可能要匯入那個模組，而非把那個管道加入 declarations
as opposed to adding the pipe to the declarations. At this point we have verified that the pipe is
這裡，我們已經驗證過此管道在該 ngModule 中可用
available in the ngModule but we're still getting the error. The next piece of code to check is the
但是仍然有錯誤。接下來是檢查該管道本身的定義
pipe definition itself and specifically the name option in the pipe decorator. Notice here how
特別是 Pipe 裝飾器中的 name 選項
the pipe name is 'shorten' but in the template it's referenced as 'truncate'. The issue can be
注意，這裡的管道名是 'shorten'，而範本中參考的是 'truncate'
resolved by fixing the mismatch. Either change the name referenced in the template or change the name
只要糾正這個小失誤，就可以解決此問題了 既可以修正範本中參考的名字，也可以修改 Pipe 裝飾器中的 name
parameter in the pipe decorator. That'll fix the issue and it brings up a good opportunity to point
修復了此問題，我們還要指出一個最佳實踐
out a best practice that will prevent issues like this from happening in the first place.
以防再發生當初那樣的錯誤
When you create a pipe in Angular, it's conventional for the pipe name
當你在 Angular 中建立一個管道時 它會遵循一個約定：管道的名字和定義它的檔名相匹配
to match the file name where it's defined. Notice how the pipe name is 'truncate' and the file name
注意，這裡的管道名是 'truncate'，而其檔名是 'truncate.pipe.ts'
is 'truncate.pipe.ts'. When using the Angular CLI, this best practice will be applied automatically.
當使用 Angular CLI 時，會自動應用此最佳實踐
Now that we know how to resolve this issue, let's do a quick review of how pipes work in Angular to
現在，我們已經知道如何解決本錯誤了 讓我們在快速過一遍 Angular 中管道的工作原理
understand why this issue happens in the first place. The role of a pipe in Angular is to
以瞭解當初為什麼會發生本錯誤 在 Angular 中，管道的角色是在範本中對值進行轉換
transform values in the template, and unlike regular method calls, Angular can optimize
與常規的方法呼叫不同，Angular 可以對管道進行最佳化
pipes. They're especially useful when you have an expression or value like a number that needs to be
當你有一個表示式或值，並且需要把它重新格式化為金額或其它格式時，它會非常有用
or you can create your own from scratch. When Angular encounters the pipe character
而且你也可以建立自己的管道集 當 Angular 在範本表示式中遇到管道符號（|）時
in a template expression, it uses the name of the pipe to determine which class has the function to
它會使用管道名來決定哪個類擁有所要執行的函式
execute. If an invalid name is provided, Angular has no way to find the corresponding function,
如果提供了無效的名字，Angular 就沒辦法找到對應的函式
but when it is valid it'll match that name to the pipe class, which implements a pipe
而當有效時，它就會根據管道的名字匹配到管道類 該類實現了管道的 transform 函式
transform function. The transform function takes the value provided from the template, along with
這個 transform 函式接受範本中提供的值以及額外引數
any additional arguments, then returns a new value which is ultimately shown to the end user.
然後返回一個新的值，新值會顯示給終端使用者
Let's go ahead and recap! When you encounter the PipeNameNotFoundError,
我們來回顧一下 當你遇到 PipeNameNotFoundError 時
it means a pipe has been referenced in a template that has either not been imported
它意味著範本中參考的某個管道或者沒有匯入過
or not been named properly. Resolve the issue by first verifying that the
或者沒有被正確命名 要解決此問題，請先驗證此管道已經匯入了或者
pipe has been imported or declared in the appropriate ngModule. If the issue remains,
在適當的 ngModule 中宣告過
check the pipe definition itself to verify that the name matches the name declared in the
如果問題仍然存在，請檢查管道本身的定義 以驗證其名字是否匹配了範本中的名字
template. For additional examples and details, reference the official Angular documentation.
欲知詳情和範例，請閱讀Angular官方文件